Allyn Fuller Collection
© 2005 University of Connecticut
Allyn Fuller Collection.
undated, 1836-1979
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center.
Fuller, Allyn.
4.5 linear feet.
Born 1889; resident of Canaan, Connecticut; railroad enthusiast; died 1971.
MSS19980175
Biography
Allyn Fuller, born in 1889, was a resident of Canaan, Connecticut. By profession, he was first a hardware store merchant and later a banker, but his passion was the history of railroads of New England, particularly those associated with the Central New England Railway, the Housatonic Railroad, and the New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad. He died in 1971.
Scope and Content
The Allyn Fuller Collection consists of papers and photographs collected by Fuller during his lifetime. The papers include train tickets, train orders, receipts, timetables, etc. The photographs show trains of the various railroads, plus scenes of railroad stations and town in Connecticut, Massachusetts, and New York.
The items are almost exclusively associated with New England railroads. The railroads represented include the Belfast and Moosehead Lake Railroad Company; the Berkshire Railroad Company; the Boston and Maine Railroad; the Canadian Pacific Railroad Company; the Central New England Railway Company; the Central New England and Western Railroad Company; the Clove Branch Rail Road Company; the Clove Springs Iron Works; the Connecticut and Passumpsic Railroad; the Connecticut Central Railroad Company; the Connecticut Western Railroad; the Danbury & Norwalk Railroad; the Dutchess and Columbia Railroad; the Edaville Railroad; the Fitchburg & Worcester Railroad; the Hartford and Connecticut Western Railroad; the Hartford and New Haven Railroad Company; the Hartford, Providence & Fishkill Railroad; the Housatonic Railroad Company; the Hudson River Day Line, the Lee and New Haven Railroad Company; the Long Island Railroad Company; the Manchester Railroad; the Naugatuck Railroad Company; the New Haven, Derby and Ansonia Railroad; the New London and Northern Railroad; the New York and Massachusetts Railway Company; the New York and New England Railroad; the New York, Boston, and Montreal Railroad; the New York, Providence & Boston Railroad; the New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad; the Newburgh, Dutchess and Connecticut Railroad; the Old Colony Railroad; the Pennsylvania, Reading & New England Railroad; the Philadelphia and Reading Railroad Company; the Philadelphia, Reading & New England Railroad Company; the Poughkeepsie & Eastern Railroad Company; the Poughkeepsie Bridge Railroad Company; the Poughkeepsie, Hartford & Boston Railroad; the Rhinebeck and Connecticut Railroad; the Stockbridge and Pittsfield Railroad Company; and the Taunton Branch Railroad.
Arrangement
The collection includes three series: papers, scrapbooks, and photographs. The papers and photographs were originally compiled in scrapbooks but were dismantled when processed and organized as separate series.
Series I: Papers, ( undated, 1836-1979 ) are organized in four groups: papers associated with specific railroads (organized alphabetically by railroad), publications, correspondence to Allyn Fuller and other related papers. Note that the majority of materials are located in boxes 1 and 2. Items in box 3 are oversize materials of railroads that are also represented in boxes 1 and 2.
Series II: Scrapbooks ( undated ) were originally compiled by Stanley Massack of New York in the 1940s. They were purchased by Allyn Fuller at an unknown date. Note that several spaces that should have a photograph within the scrapbooks are vacant. These spaces were vacant when the materials arrived in the repository.
Series III: Photographs ( undated ) are arranged in three groups: photographs of locomotives identified with specific railroads (organized alphabetically by railroad); specific stations and towns; and unidentified locomotives, towns and train wrecks. The majority of the photographs are undated and no dates are noted with the listing of the photographs in this finding aid.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to New England railroads. See especially, Charles Gunn Collection, New Haven Railroad Photographs, James Wall Collection, and Leroy Roberts Railroad Collection. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the reference desk.
Index Terms
This record series is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Organizations:
Railroads - New England; Railroads - Connecticut; Railroads - Massachusetts; Railroads - New York (state); Belfast and Moosehead Lake Railroad; Berkshire Rail-road Company; Boston and Maine Railroad; Canadian Pacific Railway Company; Central New England Railway Company; Central New England & Western Railroad Company; Clove Branch Rail Road Company; Clove Springs Iron Works; Connecticut and Passumpsic Railroad; Connecticut Central Railroad Company; Connecticut Western Railroad; Danbury & Norwalk Railroad; Dutchess and Columbia Railroad; Edaville Railroad; Fitchburg & Worcester Railroad; Hartford and Connecticut Western Railroad; Hartford and New Haven R.R. Co.; Hartford, Providence & Fishkill Railroad; Housatonic Railroad Company; Hudson River Day Line; Lee and New Haven Railroad Company; Long Island Railroad Company; Manchester Railroad; Naugatuck Railroad Company; New Haven, Derby and Ansonia Railroad; New London and Northern Railroad; New York and Massachusetts Railway Company; New York and New England Railroad; New York, Boston, and Montreal Railroad; New York, Providence & Boston Railroad; New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad; Newburgh, Dutchess and Connecticut Railroad; Old Colony Railroad; Pennsylvania, Reading & New England Railroad; Philadelphia and Reading Railroad Company; Philadelphia, Reading & New England Railroad Company; Poughkeepsie & Eastern Railroad Company; Poughkeepsie Bridge Railroad Company; Poughkeepsie, Hartford & Boston Railroad; Rhinebeck and Connecticut Railroad; Stockbridge and Pittsfield Railroad Company; Taunton Branch Railroad
Subjects:
Railroads--New England.
Document Types:
Correspondence.; Personal Papers.; Manuscripts.; Photographs.
Occupations:
Railfans.
Restrictions on Access
There are no access restrictions on this collection.
Acquisition Information
Donated by Sally Prestele, daughter of Allyn Fuller.
Detailed Description
- Series I: Papers, undated, 1836-1979
  - Items associated with specific railroads
    - Belfast and Moosehead Lake Railroad Company — ticket, undated; (1 item) (Box 1:, Folder 1)
    - Berkshire Rail-Road Company — blank stock certificate, undated; (1 item) (Box 1:, Folder 2)
    - Boston and Maine Railroad — ticket, 1958; (1 item) (Box 1:, Folder 3)
    - Canadian Pacific Railway Company — ticket, 1952; (1 item) (Box 1:, Folder 4)
    - Central New England Railway Company — unidentified papers, 1899-1921, 1965; (23 items) (Box 1:, Folder 5)
    - Central New England Railway Company — freight receipts and shipping orders, 1904-1919; (16 items) (Box 1:, Folder 6)
    - Central New England Railway Company — tickets and passes, 1899-1914; (19 items) (Box 1:, Folder 7)
    - Central New England Railway Company — timetables and bridge routes, 1900-1908; (7 items) (Box 1:, Folder 8)
    - Central New England Railway Company — train orders, 1904-1918; (10 items) (Box 1:, Folder 9)
      See also Box 3.
    - Central New England and Western Railroad Company, 1890-1891; (3 items) (Box 1:, Folder 10)
    - Clove Branch Rail Road Company — receipt, 1881; (1 item) (Box 1:, Folder 11)
    - Clove Spring Iron Works — bank checks, 1871, 1875; (2 items) (Box 1:, Folder 12)
    - Connecticut Central Railroad Company — blank stock certificate, undated; (1 item) (Box 1:, Folder 13)
    - Connecticut Western Railroad - unidentified papers, 1868-1889; (20 items) (Box 1:, Folder 14)
    - Connecticut Western Railroad - timetables, 1872, 1879; (4 items) (Box 1:, Folder 15)
    - Connecticut Western Railroad - information about stock in the company, 1871-1878; (5 items) (Box 1:, Folder 16)
    - Dutchess and Columbia Railroad, 1871-1875, 1934; (6 items) (Box 1:, Folder 17)
    - Edaville Railroad - tickets, undated, 1952; (6 items) (Box 1:, Folder 18)
    - Hartford and Connecticut Western Railroad — payroll lists and payroll receipts, 1887-1888; (4 items) (Box 1:, Folder 19)
    - Hartford and Connecticut Western Railroad — freight receipts, 1883-1889; (14 items) (Box 1:, Folder 20)
    - Hartford and Connecticut Western Railroad — train orders and unidentified items, 1886-1889, 1947; (6 items) (Box 1:, Folder 21)
    - Hartford and New Haven Railroad Company, 1856; (1 item) (Box 1:, Folder 22)
    - Housatonic Railroad Company - maps and annual reports, undated, 1836-1891; (6 items) (Box 1:, Folder 23)
    - Housatonic Railroad Company - payroll list and payroll receipt, 1865, 189?; (2 items) (Box 1:, Folder 24)
    - Housatonic Railroad Company - receipts, 1865-1883 (Box 1:, Folder 25)
    - Housatonic Railroad Company - rosters of locomotives, undated; (3 items) (Box 1:, Folder 26)
    - Housatonic Railroad Company - tickets, passes, and unidentified items, 1837-1891; (15 items) (Box 1:, Folder 27)
    - Housatonic Railroad Company - timetables, 1881-1892; (7 items) (Box 1:, Folder 28)
    - Housatonic Railroad Company - writings and general information, [1871-1890], 1965-1967; (43 items) (Box 1:, Folder 29)
    - Hudson River Day Line, 1929; (1 item) (Box 1:, Folder 30)
    - Lee and New Haven Railroad Company, 1873; (1 item) (Box 1:, Folder 31)
    - Long Island Railroad Company, 1955; (1 item) (Box 1:, Folder 32)
    - Naugatuck Railroad Company, undated, 1883; (3 items) (Box 1:, Folder 33)
    - Naugatuck Railroad Company - resolution in appreciation of the years of service of William D. Bishop, 1903; (1 item) (Box 1:, Folder 34)
    - New York and Massachusetts Railway Company, undated, 1892; (4 items) (Box 2:, Folder 35)
    - New York and New England Railroad, undated, 1882, 1896; (6 items) (Box 2:, Folder 36)
    - New York, Boston and Montreal Railway, [1873], 1874; (3 items) (Box 2:, Folder 37)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad — “Locomotives of the New Haven R.R.,” by Charles Fisher, Another of the same title by Winfield W. Robinson, 1939; (4 items) (Box 2:, Folder 38)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad — tickets and passes, 1887-1960; (49 items) (Box 2:, Folder 39)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad — train orders, 1934-1947; (4 items) (Box 2:, Folder 40)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad, 1873, 1923-1951; (10 items) (Box 2:, Folder 41)
    - Newburgh, Dutchess and Connecticut Railroad Company, 1887-1906; (15 items) (Box 2:, Folder 42)
    - Philadelphia & Reading Railroad Company, 189?, 1912; (5 items) (Box 2:, Folder 43)
    - Philadelphia, Reading & New England Railroad Company, undated, 1892-1898; (20 items) (Box 2:, Folder 44)
    - Poughkeepsie & Eastern Railway Company, 1894-1908; (13 items) (Box 2:, Folder 45)
    - Poughkeepsie Bridge Railroad Company, 1904; (1 item) (Box 2:, Folder 46)
    - Rhinebeck and Connecticut Railroad, [1878]; (1 item) (Box 2:, Folder 47)
    - Stockbridge and Pittsfield Railroad Company, 1860; (1 item) (Box 2:, Folder 48)
  - Publications
    - “The Standardization of the Track Gauge on American Railways” by J. B. Westbay. From Bulletin no. 34 of the Railway and Locomotive Historical Society, [1934]; (2 items) (Box 2:, Folder 49)
    - “New Haven and its Six Railroads,” by Sidney Withington, in Bulletin no. 56 of the Railway and Locomotive Historical Society, undated; (1 item) (Box 2:, Folder 50)
    - Bulletin: Official Publication of the National Model Railroad Association, 1975, 1979; (3 items) (Box 2:, Folder 51)
    - By-laws, Hartford Division, no. 50, order Railway Conductors, 1901; (1 item) (Box 2:, Folder 52)
    - “Centennial Message to the Citizens of Connecticut,” by Albert Wadhams, 1881; (1 item) (Box 2:, Folder 53)
    - Hartford Pocket Guide, June 1905. Includes electric and steam train schedules, (1 item) (Box 2:, Folder 54)
    - The Lure of Litchfield Hills, published by the Litchfield Hills Federation, 1945, 1967; (2 items) (Box 2:, Folder 55)
    - Pine Plains and the Railroads, by Lyndon A. Haight, published by the Little Nine Partners Historical Society of Pine Plains, N.Y., 1976; (1 item) (Box 2:, Folder 56)
    - Central New England and Predecessors Locomotive Roster, probably compiled by Fuller, undated; (3 pp.) (Box 2:, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence
    - Correspondence to Allyn Fuller, 1943-1965; (9 items) (Box 2:, Folder 58)
  - Other papers
    - Lists of contents of scrapbooks, as the materials in this collection were originally organized, undated; (16 items) (Box 2:, Folder 59)
    - List of photographs sold by the Central New England Railway RailPhoto Service, undated; (3 items) (Box 2:, Folder 60)
    - Unidentified papers, 1898-1925; (17 items) (Box 2:, Folder 61)
  - Oversize items from Boxes 1 and 2
    - Central New England and Western Railway, 1891; (1 item) (Box 3:, Folder 62)
    - Central New England Railway Company, undated, 1914; (3 items) (Box 3:, Folder 63)
    - Connecticut Western Railroad, undated, 1878, 1978; (6 items) (Box 3:, Folder 64)
    - Housatonic Railroad Company, undated, 1886-1891; (9 items) (Box 3:, Folder 65)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad, 1918; (1 item) (Box 3:, Folder 66)
    - Newburgh, Dutchess and Connecticut Railroad Company, undated; (2 items) (Box 3:, Folder 67)
    - Philadelphia and Reading Railroad, undated; (1 item) (Box 3:, Folder 68)
    - Philadelphia, Reading & New England Railroad Company, 1894, 1896; (2 items) (Box 3:, Folder 69)
    - Unidentified oversize papers, 1871-1892; (4 items) (Box 3:, Folder 70)
- Series II: Scrapbooks, undated
  - “Scenes Along the Route of the Naugatuck Railroad [and the] Waterbury and Watertown branch” (Box 4)
  - “Scenes Along the Route of the old Housatonic Railroad; New Haven & Derby R.R.; Danbury & Norwalk R.R.” (Box 5)
- Series III: Photographs, undated
  - Photographs associated with specific New England railroads
    - Cape Cod Railroad, (1 item) (Box 6:, Folder 71)
    - Central New England and Western Railway, (9 items) (Box 6:, Folder 72)
    - Central New England Railway — engines 2, 3, 4, 7, and 8, (12 items) (Box 6:, Folder 73)
    - Central New England Railway — engines 11, 12, 13, 14, 16, 17 and 19, (21 items) (Box 6:, Folder 74)
    - Central New England Railway — engines 20, 25, 26, and 27, and caboose 25, (6 items) (Box 6:, Folder 75)
    - Central New England Railway — engines 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36 and 37, (15 items) (Box 6:, Folder 76)
    - Central New England Railway — engines 40, 41, 43, 44, 45, and 48, (9 items) (Box 6:, Folder 77)
    - Central New England Railway — engines 52, 53, 54, 71, and 89, (7 items) (Box 6:, Folder 78)
    - Central New England Railway — engines 101, 106, 107, 108, 126, 155, 161, and 182, (10 items) (Box 6:, Folder 79)
    - Central New England Railway — engines 200, 201, 202, 204, 210, 211, 215, and 216, (13 items) (Box 6:, Folder 80)
    - Central New England Railway — engines 220, 221, 223, 224, 227, 229, and 230, (10 items) (Box 6:, Folder 81)
    - Central New England Railway — engines 300, 301, 403, 504, 510, 511, and 1506(?), (8 items) (Box 6:, Folder 82)
    - Central New England Railway — unidentified engines and scenes, (29 items) (Box 6:, Folder 83)
    - Clove Branch Railroad, (2 items) (Box 6:, Folder 84)
    - Connecticut and Passumpsic Railroad, (1 item) (Box 6:, Folder 85)
    - Connecticut Western Railroad Company, (19 items) (Box 6:, Folder 86)
    - Danbury & Norwalk, (1 item) (Box 6:, Folder 87)
    - Dutchess & Columbia, (6 items) (Box 6:, Folder 88)
    - Fitchburg & Worcester Railroad, (1 item) (Box 6:, Folder 89)
    - Fitchburg Railroad, (1 item) (Box 6:, Folder 90)
    - Hartford & Connecticut Western, (18 items) (Box 6:, Folder 91)
    - Hartford, Providence & Fishkill Railroad, (7 items) (Box 6:, Folder 92)
    - Housatonic Railroad - named engines, including “Useful” (#1), “Samuel Willetts” (#2), “W.H. Barnum” (#3), “Charles A. Averill” (#4), and “Horace Nichols” (#7), (9 items) (Box 6:, Folder 93)
    - Housatonic Railroad - named engines, including “Lee” (#8), “New Milford” (#9), “Bridgeport” (#10), “Berkshire” (#11), “N. Thayer” (#12), “Great Barrington” (#13), and “David S. Draper” (#15), (13 items) (Box 6:, Folder 94)
    - Housatonic Railroad - engines 17, 19, 20, 23, 24, 27, 35, 38, 52, and 56, (13 items) (Box 6:, Folder 95)
    - Housatonic Railroad — unidentified engines, (15 items) (Box 6:, Folder 96)
    - Housatonic Railroad — stations and scenes, including the Housatonic Falls in Falls Village, Connecticut, (20 items) (Box 6:, Folder 97)
    - Manchester Railroad, (1 item) (Box 6:, Folder 98)
    - Naugatuck Railroad, (6 items) (Box 6:, Folder 99)
    - New Haven and Derby Railroad, (1 item) (Box 6:, Folder 100)
    - New Haven and Hartford Railroad, (1 item) (Box 6:, Folder 101)
    - New Haven, Derby and Ansonia Railroad, (1 item) (Box 6:, Folder 102)
    - New London and Northern Railroad, (1 item) (Box 6:, Folder 103)
    - New York and New England Railroad, (4 items) (Box 6:, Folder 104)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad — engines 26, 58, 78, 128, 136, 168, 173, 183, 191, 209, 224, 240, 291, and 294, (17 items) (Box 7:, Folder 105)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad — engines 303, 315, 332, 339, 365, 384, 386, 392, 393, 432, 468, 470, 473, 480, 481, 501, 508, 538, and 542, (22 items) (Box 7:, Folder 106)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad — engines 816, 818, 820, 827, 836, 842, 847, 892(?), and 970, (13 items) (Box 7:, Folder 107)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad — engines 1001, 1006, 1008, 1009, 1071, 1094, 1101, 1111, 1200, 1271, 1273, 1274, and 1281, (15 items) (Box 7:, Folder 108)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad — engines 1301, 1304, 1313, 1327, 1340, 1349, 1359, 1388, 1393 and 1399, (17 items) (Box 7:, Folder 109)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad — engines 1400, 1401, 1403, 1405, 1407, 1408, 1409, 1411, and 1414, (15 items) (Box 7:, Folder 110)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad — engines 1504, 1506, 1531, 1596, 1636, and 1670, (8 items) (Box 7:, Folder 111)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad — engines 2140, 2310, 2375, 2424 and 2549, (5 items) (Box 7:, Folder 112)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad — engines 3010, 3020, 3205, 3213, 3248, 3303, 3320, 3324, 3327, 3330, 3338, 3339(?), 3550, 3562, and 9001, (21 items) (Box 7:, Folder 113)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad — electric trains, (7 items) (Box 7:, Folder 114)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad — diesel engines, (9 items) (Box 7:, Folder 115)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad - unidentified scenes and engines, (47 items) (Box 7:, Folder 116)
    - New York, Providence & Boston Railroad, (4 items) (Box 7:, Folder 117)
    - Newburgh, Dutchess & Connecticut Railroad, (16 items) (Box 7:, Folder 118)
    - Old Colony Railroad, (1 item) (Box 7:, Folder 119)
    - Pennsylvania, Poughkeepsie & Boston, (1 item) (Box 7:, Folder 120)
    - Phildelphia & Reading Railroad, (2 items) (Box 7:, Folder 121)
    - Philadelphia, Reading & New England Railroad — engines 2(?), 4, 5, 7, 8, 11, 13, 14, 16, 18, and 19, (21 items) (Box 7:, Folder 122)
    - Philadelphia, Reading & New England Railroad — engines 22, 23, 25, 28, 30, 32, 34, 35, 36, 37, 39, 1254, 1274, 1275, and 1905, (22 items) (Box 7:, Folder 123)
    - Poughkeepsie & Eastern Railroad, (9 items) (Box 7:, Folder 124)
    - Poughkeepsie, Hartford & Boston Railroad, (4 items) (Box 7:, Folder 125)
    - Taunton Branch Railroad, (1 item) (Box 7:, Folder 126)
  - Photographs of Connecticut railroad stations or scenes
    - Bethel, Connecticut, (2 item) (Box 7:, Folder 127)
    - Bridgeport, Connecticut, (4 items) (Box 7:, Folder 128)
    - Canaan, Connecticut, (15 items) (Box 7:, Folder 129)
    - Colebrook, Connecticut, (1 item) (Box 7:, Folder 130)
    - Collinsville, Connecticut, (3 items) (Box 7:, Folder 131)
    - Cornwall Bridge, Connecticut, (3 items) (Box 7:, Folder 132)
    - East Canaan, Connecticut, (7 items) (Box 7:, Folder 133)
    - East Hartford, Connecticut, (1 item) (Box 7:, Folder 134)
    - Falls Village, Connecticut, (2 items) (Box 7:, Folder 135)
    - Hartford, Connecticut, (4 items) (Box 7:, Folder 136)
    - Lakeville, Connecticut, (3 items) (Box 7:, Folder 137)
    - Naugatuck, Connecticut, (1 item) (Box 7:, Folder 138)
    - New Milford, Connecticut, (3 items) (Box 7:, Folder 139)
    - Norfolk, Connecticut, (1 item) (Box 7:, Folder 140)
    - Norfolk Summit, Connecticut, (1 item) (Box 7:, Folder 141)
    - Pine Grove Station, Connecticut, (1 item) (Box 7:, Folder 142)
    - Ridgefield, Connecticut, (1 item) (Box 7:, Folder 143)
    - Salisbury, Connecticut, (3 items) (Box 7:, Folder 144)
    - Stepney, Connecticut, (3 item) (Box 7:, Folder 145)
    - Summit, Connecticut, (1 item) (Box 7:, Folder 146)
    - Taconic, Connecticut, (1 item) (Box 7:, Folder 147)
    - Tariffville, Connecticut, (1 item) (Box 7:, Folder 148)
    - Thomaston, Connecticut, (1 item) (Box 8:, Folder 149)
    - Twin Lakes, Connecticut, (7 items) (Box 8:, Folder 150)
    - Weatogue, Connecticut, (2 items) (Box 8:, Folder 151)
    - Winsted, Connecticut, (3 items) (Box 8:, Folder 152)
  - Photographs of Massachusetts railroad stations
    - Ashley Falls, Massachusetts, (1 item) (Box 8:, Folder 153)
    - Feeding Hills, Massachusetts, (1 item) (Box 8:, Folder 154)
    - Pittsfield, Massachusetts, (1 item) (Box 8:, Folder 155)
  - Photographs of New York railroad stations or scenes
    - Ancramdale, New York, (1 item) (Box 8:, Folder 156)
    - Bangall, New York, (1 item) (Box 8:, Folder 157)
    - Boston Corners, New York, (1 item) (Box 8:, Folder 158)
    - Clinton Corners, New York, (2 items) (Box 8:, Folder 159)
    - Copake, New York, (3 items) (Box 8:, Folder 160)
    - Fishkill, New York, (1 item) (Box 8:, Folder 161)
    - Glenham, New York, (1 item) (Box 8:, Folder 162)
    - Hopewell Junction, New York, (3 items) (Box 8:, Folder 163)
    - McIntyre, New York, (1 item) (Box 8:, Folder 163a)
    - Matteawan, New York, (1 item) (Box 8:, Folder 164)
    - Maybrook, New York, (2 items) (Box 8:, Folder 165)
    - Millbrook, New York, (1 item) (Box 8:, Folder 166)
    - Millerton, New York, (2 items) (Box 8:, Folder 167)
    - Pine Plains, New York, (2 items) (Box 8:, Folder 168)
    - Pleasant Valley, New York, (1 item) (Box 8:, Folder 169)
    - Poughkeepsie, New York, (3 items) (Box 8:, Folder 170)
    - Silvernails, New York, (5 items) (Box 8:, Folder 171)
    - Stanfordville, New York, (2 items) (Box 8:, Folder 172)
    - Willowbrook, New York, (1 item) (Box 8:, Folder 173)
  - Other photographs
    - General unidentified trains, stations, and scenes, (19 items) (Box 8:, Folder 174)
    - Railroad wrecks for unidentified trains, (14 items) (Box 8:, Folder 175)
    - Portraits, (9 items) (Box 8:, Folder 176)